https://mogulski.com.au/privacy-policy/

Top
Privacy PolicyMogul Ski World respects your privacy and voluntarily adheres to the National Privacy Principles under the Privacy Act 1998 (Cth).What Personal Information we collect?Any personal information that Mogul Ski World obtains from the Customer, or about the customer from its representatives, will only be collected to enable us to provide you with our best services as a Travel Agency.We receive, collect and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way.We may use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information and methods used to browse away from the pageUsage and SharingInformation submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you with the information you are seeking or providing ongoing services. It may also be provided to contracted service providers relating to our communications with you.We will never share or sell individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law.Protecting your privacyProtecting your privacy online has never been more paramount. We use security measures to protect against the loss and misuse and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure of the data we collect.Measures to ensure accuracyMogul Ski World will take reasonable steps to ensure the personal information collected, used or disclosed is accurate and up-to-date.Personal information used for future communicationsFrom time to time we may use the information that we have collected from you to send mail or email to you containing travel information or news. We are mindful that not all customers want to receive future communications and we will make it very easy for you to opt out of these communications should you no longer wish to receive them. VISIT UTAH AND DELTA AIR LINES SOCIAL MEDIA COMPETITIONTERMS & CONDITIONSThe promoter is: Mogul Ski World Pty Ltd (ABN no. 12007317348) whose registered office is at 1/464 High Street, Prahran, VIC 3181The competition is open to residents of Australia aged 18 years or over except employees of Mogul Ski World and their close relatives and anyone otherwise connected with the organisation or judging of the competition.There is no entry fee and no purchase necessary to enter this competition.By entering this competition, an entrant is indicating his/her agreement to be bound by these terms and conditions.Route to entry for the competition and details of how to enter are via https://www.instagram.com/mogulskiworld  and https://www.facebook.com/MogulSkiWorldClosing date for entry is midnight AEST on 30 September, After this date, no further entries to the competition will be permitted.No responsibility can be accepted for entries not received for whatever reason.The promoter reserves the right to cancel or amend the competition and these terms and conditions without notice in the event of a catastrophe, war, civil or military disturbance, act of God or any actual or anticipated breach of any applicable law or regulation or any other event outside of the promoter’s control. Any changes to the competition will be notified to entrants as soon as possible by the promoter.The promoter is not responsible for inaccurate prize details supplied to any entrant by any third party connected with this competition.The winner will be announced 9 October on Instagram and Facebook and contacted via email. If the winner cannot be contacted or do not claim the prize within 14 days of notification, we reserve the right to withdraw the prize from the winner and pick a replacement winner.The promoter will notify the winner when and where the prize can be collected / is delivered.The promoter’s decision in respect of all matters to do with the competition will be final and no correspondence will be entered into.The competition and these terms and conditions will be governed by Australian law and any disputes will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Australia.The winner agrees to the use of his/her name and image in any publicity material, as well as their entry. Any personal data relating to the winner or any other entrants will be used solely in accordance with current Australian data protection legislation and will not be disclosed to a third party without the entrant’s prior consent.The winner’s name will be available 28 days after closing date by emailing the following address: marketing@mogulski.com.auEntry into the competition will be deemed as acceptance of these terms and conditions.You are providing your information to Mogul Ski World, Visit Utah and Delta Air Lines only and not to any other party.Mogul Ski World will judge the competition and decide on the winner, which will be selected based on creativity and merit.Mogul Ski World’s decision as to those able to take part and selection of winners is final. No correspondence relating to the competition will be entered into.Mogul Ski World shall have the right, at its sole discretion and at any time, to change or modify these terms and conditions, such change shall be effective immediately upon posting to this web page.Mogul Ski World also reserves the right to cancel the competition if circumstances arise outside of its control.Prize validity:Prizes are non-transferable and non-redeemable for cashAccommodation, lift tickets, dining vouchers and Heber Valley attraction admissions are valid until 31 March 2022 and are subject to blackout dates and availability at time of booking. DELTA AIR LINES FLIGHTS:The winner will be provided a prize certificate from Delta Air Lines. To redeem, the winner will need the reference code, certificate number, redemption code and booking class specified on the certificate.The voucher is redeemable through salesSupportSYDGSA@delta.com, using the Delta Reference found on the certificateReservations must be made and tickets issued prior to departure. Tickets must be issued within 24 hours of making reservations. The number of seats available for this offer is limited.All taxes, fees and surcharges are the responsibility of the passenger and will need to be paid by credit card at time of flight bookingPrize certificate must be redeemed and ticket issued by 30 September 2021, with travel to be completed within 21 months of issue. Extensions will not be granted under any circumstances.Stopovers of more than 24 hours for transoceanic travel are not permitted.Ticket is non-transferrable and cannot be redeemed for cash.Travel is permitted on Delta, Delta Shuttle and certain Delta Connection Carriers subject to availabilityTravel is not permitted on any Code Share flights, AA Eagle, Freedom Airlines and Shuttle AmericaAustralian Travellers are required to obey by the following travel restrictions:– Travel is not permitted on Friday, Saturday and Sunday departures– Flights are subject to availability on class and blackout dates applyAny changes to booking once ticketed will incur a change fee per passenger, per change and any change is subject to availability.No name changes permitted after ticketingDelta Air Lines terms and conditions of varriage apply to the ticketPrize certificates or tickets may not be sold or offered for re-sale at a premium (including via online auction sites) or used for advertising, promotion or other commercial purposes or to enhance the demand for other goods or services, either by the original recipient or any subsequent bearer. If a prize certificate or ticket is sold or used in these conditions, it will be cancelled at Delta Air Lines sole discretion.Passengers are responsible for all other ancillary costs. Travel insurance is highly recommended to protect against additional cost incurrent in the event of unforeseen circumstances.Tickets cannot be upgraded and are not valid to earn SkyMiles or status creditsIt is the sole responsibility of the traveller to ensure their entry into the USA, at their own expense, including ensuring all necessary passports are valid for six (6) months from date of travel and visas, travel authorisations including an Electronic System for Travel Authorization (ESTA) (if applicable), medical advice and recommended vaccinations and immunisations have been obtained prior to travel and, if required, on or by a date nominated by the Promoter. Failure to do so may result in the prize being forfeited. The Promoter makes no representation as to the safety of the USA and it is the responsibility of the winners to check the travel advice issued by the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade at smartraveller.gov.au and assess the safety of USA prior to travel. Join Newsletter To receive our best deals
